Guide to the David Benjamin Mixner Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Subject Files, 1958-2005; Series III
  - Colorado Project/Common Cause
    - Tax reform, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 175)
    - "Third Force" [newsletter], 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 176)
    - Utilities, 1972, undated (Box 40, Folder 177)
  - Community Voter Guide, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 178)
  - Constitutional amendment [federal marriage amendment], 2004 (Box 40, Folder 179 - 181)
  - Dakota Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 182)
  - Daschle, Tom
    - General, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 183)
    - Commissions, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 184)
  - Davis [Gray] for Governor, 1998, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 185)
  - Davis [Gray] for Senate, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 186)
  - Davis, Gray
    - Governor's office, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 187)
    - Staff [clipping], 1999 (Box 41, Folder 188)
  - Dean [Howard] for Governor, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 189)
  - Dean [Howard] for President, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 190)
  - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee (DCCC)
    - General, 1999-2002 (Box 41, Folder 191 - 194)
    - Advisory committees, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 195)
    - Dinner committee, undated (Box 41, Folder 196)
    - September dinner, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 197)
    - Walk, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 198)
  - Democratic National Committee (DNC)
    - General, 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 199 - 200)
    - Lists, undated (Box 41, Folder 201)
  - Democratic National Convention
    - General, 1968, [1972?], 2000 (Box 41, Folder 202)
    - Boston, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 203)
    - Credentials, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 204)
    - DCCC, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 205)
    - Events, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 206)
    - Reservations, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 207)
    - Schedules, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 208)
  - Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee (DSCC)
    - General, 2000-2004 (Box 41, Folder 209 - 211)
    - Checks, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 212)
    - Invite [dinner], 2000 (Box 41, Folder 213)
    - Kennedy [Edward] event, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 214 - 217)
    - Tables, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 218)
  - Digital Entertainment Network
    - General, 1997-2000 (Box 41, Folder 219)
    - Business plan, 1997, undated (Box 41, Folder 220)
    - Press, 1999 (Box 41, Folder 221)
    - Proposal, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 222)
    - Shows, undated (Box 41, Folder 223)
  - Doctors Without Borders, 2003, undated (Box 41, Folder 224)
  - Domestic partnership, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 225)
  - Duran [John]-election returns, undated (Box 41, Folder 226)
  - East/West Institute, 2003 February (Box 42, Folder 227)
  - Edwards, [John], 2000-2002 (Box 42, Folder 228)
  - Elections-1998, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 229)
  - Elizabeth Glaser Pediatric AIDS Foundation, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 230)
  - Empire State Pride agenda, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 231)
  - Employment Non-Discrimination Act, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 232)
  - Encore Media Group, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 233)
  - Farber [Michael] for Congress, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 234)
  - Feinstein [Dianne]-AIDS Advisory Committee, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 235)
  - Flanagan [Edward] for Senate, 1998-2000 (Box 42, Folder 236)
  - Foundation for Civil Rights, 1992, 1995-1996 (Box 42, Folder 237)
  - Friends of Arlo Smith, plan, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 238)
  - Garamendi, John
    - General, 1991-1993 (Box 42, Folder 239)
    - AIDS, undated (Box 42, Folder 240)
    - Auto insurance reform, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 241)
    - Clippings, 1991-1994 (Box 42, Folder 242)
    - Governor, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 243)
    - Healthcare, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 244)
    - Memos, 1992, undated (Box 42, Folder 245)
    - Patti, undated (Box 42, Folder 246)
    - Workers compensation, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 247)
  - Garcetti [Gil] for District Attorney, 1992, undated (Box 42, Folder 248)
  - Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation (GLAAD), 1995-1998 (Box 42, Folder 249)
  - Gay and Lesbian History Museum, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 250)
  - Gay and Lesbian Medical Association, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 251)
  - Gay-Cable
    - General, 1998, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 252)
    - Sanders, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 253)
  - Gay Democrats, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 254)
  - Gay Financial Network, 1998, undated (Box 42, Folder 255)
  - Gay Games, 1992-2001 (Box 42, Folder 256)
  - Gay hate crimes, 1994, 1999, undated (Box 42, Folder 257)
  - The Gay, Lesbian, and Straight Teachers Network, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 258)
  - Gay marketing, 1997, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 259)
  - Gay marriage, 1996, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 260)
  - Gay-press, 1998, 2000, undated (Box 42, Folder 261)
  - Gay Pride events, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 262)
  - Gay radio station, 1997, undated (Box 42, Folder 263)
  - Gay rights articles, 1987-1988, undated (Box 42, Folder 264)
  - Gay youth, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 265)
  - Gay.com
    - General, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 266)
    - Barclay, Paris, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 267)
    - Birch, Elizabeth, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 268)
    - Bond, Brian, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 269)
    - Bond, Julian, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 270)
    - Clinton, William Jefferson, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 271)
    - Cohen, Bruce, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 272)
      General note
      See also: Series VI. Audiovisual, 1924, 1964-2004 Box 68
    - Corporate, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 273)
    - Daschle, Thomas, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 274)
    - De la Huerte, Christian, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 275)
    - Dreyfus, Julia Louis, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 276)
    - Editorial, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 277)
    - Gephardt, Richard, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 278)
    - Gore, Albert, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 279)
    - Human Rights Watch, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 280)
    - Interfaith Alliance, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 281)
    - Kennedy, Edward, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 282)
    - Light, Judith, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 283)
    - MacLaine, Shirley, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 284)
    - Matlin, Mary, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 285)
    - Memos, 2000-2001 (Box 43, Folder 286)
    - Mixner, David B. interview, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 287)
    - Osborn, Torie, 2000-2001 (Box 43, Folder 288)
    - Pallone, David, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 289)
    - Publicity, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 290)
    - Reports, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 291)
    - Roberts, Ian, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 292)
    - Stephanopoulos, George, 2000-2001 (Box 43, Folder 293)
    - Wendle, Kevin, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 294)
    - West Virginia, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 295)
    - Writers, 2001 (Box 43, Folder 296)
  - Gays-military, 1991-1995 (Box 43, Folder 297)
  - Gephardt, Richard
    - Emails, notes, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 298)
    - Fundraising, 1998, undated (Box 44, Folder 299)
    - Gephardt for President
      - General, 1998, 2001-2004 (Box 44, Folder 300 - 305)
      - Gay, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 306 - 307)
      - Gay endorsements, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 308)
      - Hindery [Leo] Event, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 309)
      - September event, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 310)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001-2002 (Box 44, Folder 311)
  - Get Challenged, 1997, undated (Box 44, Folder 312)
  - Global Business Council on AIDS, 2002-2003, undated (Box 44, Folder 313)
  - Gore [Albert] for President, 1999-2000 (Box 44, Folder 314)
  - Great Peace March for Global Disarmament, 1985-1986, undated (Box 44, Folder 315)
    See also: Series III. Subject Files, 1958-2005 Folder 495
  - Green Party, 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 316)
  - Hale House, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 317)
  - Harvard AIDS Institute, 1993, undated (Box 45, Folder 318)
  - Harvard-education, 1992-1993, undated (Box 45, Folder 319)
  - Hindery, Leo
    - General, 2000-2002, undated (Box 45, Folder 320)
    - AIDS, Africa, 2001-2002 (Box 45, Folder 321)
    - Background, 1999-2000 (Box 45, Folder 322)
    - Constitution project, 2004-2005, undated (Box 45, Folder 323)
    - Contribution, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 324)
    - Donations, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 325)
    - England, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 326)
    - Gephardt [Richard] event, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 327)
    - Global Business Council on AIDS, 2001-2004 (Box 45, Folder 328 - 329)
    - Hurricane OpEd, 2005, undated (Box 45, Folder 330)
    - Kerry [John], 2004 (Box 45, Folder 331)
    - Labor, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 332)
    - Memos, 2001-2004 (Box 45, Folder 333 - 337)
    - Mixner [David], 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 338)
    - Oates/Shrum event, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 339)
    - OpEd, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 340)
    - Pine Ridge, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 341)
    - Political, 2000-2004 (Box 46, Folder 342 - 344)
    - Senate, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 345)
    - Shrum [Robert], 2000 (Box 46, Folder 346)
    - Speeches, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 347)
    - Transatlantic Partnership Against AIDS (TPAA) event, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 348)
    - Victory Fund, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 349)
    - Washington, D.C., 2001 (Box 46, Folder 350)
  - Human Rights Campaign (HRC)
    - General, 1996-1997 (Box 46, Folder 351)
    - Hawaii, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 352)
    - HRC Fund
      - General, 1993-1996, undated (Box 46, Folder 353 - 354)
      - Employment, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 355)
  - Human Rights Watch
    - General, 1999-2000 (Box 46, Folder 356)
    - Romania, 1998 (Box 46, Folder 357)
  - Independent counsel, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 358)
  - Indonesia research, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 359)
  - Initiatives, 1993-1994 (Box 46, Folder 360)
  - International AIDS Trust, 2001-2003 (Box 46, Folder 361)
  - International AIDS Vaccine Initiative, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 362)
  - International Gay/Lesbian Human Rights Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 46, Folder 363)
  - Ireland conference, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 364)
  - Isbell, Michael, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 365)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines [convention rally], 1964 (Box 46, Folder 366)
  - Judges, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 367)
  - Kaitz Foundation, 1993, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 368)
  - Kennedy, Edward
    - General, 1968-1970, 2000-2001, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 369)
    - Kennedy for Senate
      - Event
        - General, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 370)
        - Checks, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 371)
      - Interview, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 372)
  - Kennedy, John/Lyndon Baines Johnson, 1963-1964 (Box 46, Folder 373)
  - Kennedy Townsend, Kathleen for Governor, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 374)
  - Kennedy, Maxwell, 2001 (Box 46, Folder 375)
  - Kennedy, Patrick, 2001-2002 (Box 46, Folder 376)
  - Kerrey [Robert] for Senate, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 377)
  - Kerry, John
    - Finance committee, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 378)
    - Fundraising, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 379)
    - Gay, 2002, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 380 - 382)
    - Gay, lesbian, bisexual, AIDS issues, 2003-2004 (Box 47, Folder 383)
    - Kerry for President, 2002-2004 (Box 47, Folder 384)
    - Kerry for Senate, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 385)
    - "Ripples of Hope", 2004 (Box 47, Folder 386 - 390)
  - Kessler, David, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 391)
  - Kol Ami Award, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 392)
  - Kuehl [Sheila] for Assembly, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 393)
  - Labor Day, Los Angeles, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 394)
  - Liberty Media, 2001 (Box 47, Folder 395)
  - Life Lobby, 1992, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 396)
  - Lists-internet, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 397)
  - Los Angeles-election results, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 398)
  - Los Angeles Gay and Lesbian Community Center, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 399)
  - Los Angeles Police Department, 1998-1999 (Box 47, Folder 400)
  - Los Angeles Times Book Review, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 401)
  - Love-ins, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 402)
  - March in Washington, 2000 (Box 48, Folder 403)
  - Marmillon, Val
    - Finance committee, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 404)
    - Marmillon for Congress, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 405)
  - Mauro [Gary] for Governor, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 406)
  - Mayor's Alliance for a Safer Los Angeles, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 407 - 408)
  - McCall [Carl] for Governor, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 409)
  - McCarthy, Eugene, 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 410)
  - McGovern Commission, 1969-1970 (Box 48, Folder 411)
  - McGreevey, James
    - General, 2004-2005 (Box 48, Folder 412)
    - Memos and letters, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 413 - 414)
    - OpEd, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 415)
    - Speaking, 2005 (Box 48, Folder 416)
  - McHale [Michael] for Congress, 2001 (Box 48, Folder 417)
  - Metropolitan Community Church, 1995-1997 (Box 48, Folder 418 - 419)
  - Millenium Coalition, 1999 (Box 48, Folder 420)
  - Miller, Tony
    - General, 1993-1994 (Box 48, Folder 421)
    - Billboards, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 422)
    - Boycott, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 423)
    - Bud boycott, 1998 (Box 48, Folder 424)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Memos, 1993-1996 (Box 48, Folder 425)
    - "1960s", 1958, 1969-1970, undated (Box 48, Folder 426 - 427)
  - Mixner, David B.
    - Contributions/Contributors, 1999-2002 (Box 48, Folder 428 - 430)
    - David B. Mixner Associates consultants' bills, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 431)
    - Entertainment list, 1997 (Box 48, Folder 432)
    - JET [Air Combat USA], 2002 (Box 48, Folder 433)
    - Speaking-William Morris, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 434)
  - Mixner/Scott-campaign work, 1982-1985 (Box 48, Folder 435)
  - Montana, 1995 (Box 48, Folder 436)
  - Municipal Elections Committee of Los Angeles (MECLA) [one newsletter], 1982 (Box 48, Folder 437)
  - Names Project
    - General, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 438 - 439)
    - Budget, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 440)
  - National Action Corps, Circa 1969 (Box 49, Folder 441)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP)
    - AIDS Video Project
      - General, 1998-2000 (Box 49, Folder 442 - 443)
      - Biographies, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 444)
      - Cable Positive, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 445)
      - Caterer, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 446)
      - Distribution, 1999-2000 (Box 49, Folder 447 - 448)
      - Fall lunch, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 449)
      - Invitations, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 450)
      - Invoices, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 451)
      - Key messages, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 452)
      - Leaders guide, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 453)
      - Media, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 454)
      - Names, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 455)
      - October 14th, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 456)
      - Premier, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 457)
      - Press, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 458)
      - Proposal, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 459)
      - Review process, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 460)
      - Speakers reception, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 461)
      - White House, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 462)
    - Memos, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 463)
    - National convention, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 464)
    - Telecommunications, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 465)
  - National Association of People with AIDS (NAPWA), 2002 (Box 49, Folder 466)
  - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 49, Folder 467)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force (NGLTF), 1994-1995 (Box 49, Folder 468)
  - Needle exchange, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 469)
  - New Democratic Coalition, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 470)
  - New York AIDS dinner, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 471)
  - Nixon White House, 1968-1969 (Box 49, Folder 472)
  - "No on Knight"
    - General, 1999-2000 (Box 49, Folder 473)
    - Roast, 1999 (Box 49, Folder 474)
  - "No on 64"
    - Budget summaries, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 475)
    - Campaign report, 1986 November 30 (Box 49, Folder 476)
    - Legal, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 477)
    - Polling, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 478)
  - Northwest, 1998-1999 (Box 49, Folder 479)
  - Nunn research, 1992-1993 (Box 49, Folder 480)
  - Out magazine, 1994-1995 (Box 50, Folder 481)
  - Pallotta, 1994, 1997, 2002, undated (Box 50, Folder 482 - 484)
  - Parade Pictures, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 485)
  - Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (P-FLAG), 1993 (Box 50, Folder 486)
  - People's Park, undated (Box 50, Folder 487)
  - Peter Scott Scholarship Fund, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 488)
  - Phillips, Preston, Circa 1993 (Box 50, Folder 489)
  - Pink Triangle, 1984, 1989, 1995-1997 (Box 50, Folder 490)
  - Pinkala [Ken] case, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 491)
  - Political events/receptions [miscellaneous invitations], 1970, undated (Box 50, Folder 492)
  - "Political Wag.com", 2000 (Box 50, Folder 493)
  - Pride fund, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 494)
  - PRO Peace
    - General, 1984-1986, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 495)
    - Annison, Patricia M.-letters and memos, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 496)
    - Audit, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 497)
    - Bankruptcy, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 498)
    - Camp plans, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 499)
    - Clippings, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 500)
    - Colorado organizing, 1985-1986 (Box 50, Folder 501)
    - Departure-Los Angeles Coliseum (no!), 1986 (Box 50, Folder 502)
    - Endorsements, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 503)
    - Financial, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 504 - 505)
    - March application, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 506)
    - March information, 1985, undated (Box 50, Folder 507)
    - March route organization, 1986 (Box 50, Folder 508)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 50, Folder 509)
    - Newsletter, 1985-1986 (Box 50, Folder 510)
    - Organizational meeting, 1984 October 11 (Box 50, Folder 511)
  - Project Open Hand, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 512)
  - Public Response Associates
    - "Printout of the Results of a Statewide Survey", 1986 October (Box 50, Folder 513)
    - Survey, 1986 July (Box 50, Folder 514)
  - Publishers, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 515)
  - Q-Spirit, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 516)
  - Rainbow Network, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 517)
  - Rath Foundation, 1994-1996 (Box 50, Folder 518 - 519)
  - Reiner Initiative
    - General, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 520)
    - Contract, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 521)
    - Press plan, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 522)
    - Strategy, 1998 (Box 50, Folder 523)
  - Robb, Charles, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 524)
  - Sanctuary Project, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 525)
  - Schipske [Gerrie], 2000 (Box 50, Folder 526)
  - Servicemembers Legal Defense Network, 1995-1999 (Box 50, Folder 527 - 529)
  - Shuster, Todd, 2001 (Box 50, Folder 530)
  - Stonewall 25, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 531)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), undated (Box 50, Folder 532)
  - Tele-Communications, Inc. (TCI)
    - Diversity, 1998-1999 (Box 51, Folder 533)
    - Memos, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 534)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP)
      - General, 1998-1999 (Box 51, Folder 535)
      - Research, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 536)
    - Push, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 537)
    - Shepard Project, 1998-1999 (Box 51, Folder 538)
  - Transatlantic Partnership Against AIDS [also known as Russia/US Working Group]
    - General, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 539 - 541)
    - AIDS in the workplace, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 542)
    - Basic, Circa 2003 (Box 51, Folder 543)
    - Boards, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 544)
    - Business/labor summit, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 545)
    - Corporate, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 546)
    - Final report, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 547)
    - Funding, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 548)
    - Labor, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 549)
    - Legal, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 550)
    - Parliamentarians, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 551)
    - Press, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 552)
    - Programs, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 553)
    - Russia/US Working Group
      - General, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 554 - 555)
      - Articles, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 556)
      - Biographies, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 557)
      - Board, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 558)
      - Breakfast, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 559 - 561)
      - Budgets, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 562)
      - DC/June, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 563 - 566)
      - Funding, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 567)
      - Hindery, Leo, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 568)
      - Key people, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 569)
      - Moscow [conference in Moscow, May 15-16, 2003] (Box 52, Folder 570 - 572)
      - "Near forum", 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 573)
      - Partners, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 574)
      - Proposals, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 575)
      - Timelines, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 576)
  - United Airlines
    - The Center, 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 577)
    - San Francisco, 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 578)
  - United Nations Foundation, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 579)
  - United States Holocaust Museum
    - General, 1996-1999 (Box 52, Folder 580)
    - Articles/brochures, 1993-1996 (Box 52, Folder 581)
    - Basle Ryan, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 52, Folder 582)
    - Committee, 1994-1996 (Box 52, Folder 583)
    - D. C. event, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 584)
    - Documentary, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 585)
    - Gonda event, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 586)
    - Lists, 1995-1996 (Box 52, Folder 587)
    - Newsletter, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 588)
    - Offices, 1994-1995 (Box 52, Folder 589)
    - United States Holocaust Museum Project
      - General, 1993-1995 (Box 52, Folder 590)
      - Memos, 1993-1996 (Box 52, Folder 591)
  - University of California, Los Angeles
    - AIDS Institute, 1993-1994 (Box 53, Folder 592)
    - Freedom Project
      - General, 1994-1996, undated (Box 53, Folder 593 - 596)
      - Background
        - Part I, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 597)
        - Part II, 1986-1993 (Box 54)
        - Part III, 1982-1994
      - Chancellor, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 598)
      - Clippings, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 599)
      - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 600)
      - Legal, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 601)
      - Memos, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 602 - 603)
      - Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 55, Folder 604)
      - Press release, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 605)
  - Victory Fund
    - General, 1991-2001 (Box 55, Folder 606 - 611)
    - Approved candidates, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 612)
    - Audit, 1993 (Box 55, Folder 613)
    - Board members, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 614)
    - Board minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 615)
    - Budget, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 616)
    - California, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 617)
    - Contributors, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 618)
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 619)
    - Fundraising, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 620)
    - Hindery [Leo] event, 2002 (Box 55, Folder 621)
    - Lists, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 622)
    - Materials, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 623)
    - Membership, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 624)
    - Memos, 1991-1994 (Box 55, Folder 625)
    - Mixner, David B., event, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 626)
    - Other candidates, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 627)
    - Political, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 628)
    - Press, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 629)
    - Search, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 630)
    - Shrum/Oates event, 2001 (Box 56, Folder 631)
    - Talking points, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 632)
    - 2004 event, 2004-2005 (Box 56, Folder 633 - 635)
    - Wexler [Anne] event, 2003 (Box 56, Folder 636)
  - Vietnam Moratorium, 1969-1970 (Box 56, Folder 637)
  - Wachs [Joel] for Mayor, 2000-2001 (Box 56, Folder 638)
  - Wasson, Marcus [law office], 1988-1989 (Box 56, Folder 639)
  - Waterford Project, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 640)
  - Waxman [Henry A.] event, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 641)
  - Wellstone [Paul] event, 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 642)
  - White, David, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 643)
  - White House
    - General, 1993-2001 (Box 56, Folder 644 - 647)
    - AIDS summit, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 648)
    - Commissions, 1998-2000 (Box 56, Folder 649)
    - Fellowship, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 650)
    - Letters, 1994-1995 (Box 56, Folder 651)
    - Staff, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 652)
  - Window Corp.
    - General, 1996-1997 (Box 56, Folder 653 - 654)
    - Window Media, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 655)
  - Women's equality poll, 1995 (Box 56, Folder 656)
  - Worker's compensation, 1985-1986, undated (Box 56, Folder 657)
- Writings, 1989-2003; Series IV
  The series is arranged in three groups: books, screenplays, and speeches.
  - Books
    - Brave Journeys
      See also: Series VI. Audiovisual, 1924, 1964-2004 Box 67
      - Published copy, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - General, 1999-2000 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Bailey, Dennis, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Reviews, 2000-2001 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Stranger Among Friends
      - Published copy, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - General [including earlier drafts and outlines], 1990, 1994-1996, undated (Box 58, Folder 6 - 9)
      - Acknowledgments, 1996, undated (Box 58, Folder 10 - 11)
      - Annison, Patsy [book comments], 1994, undated (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Book cover, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 13 - 14)
      - Book tour, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Harris, Anne, 1996 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - Heros, 1996, undated (Box 58, Folder 17)